subiz.com 2019-06-04

# Live chat solution for website | Subiz Privacy Policy

**Subiz respects and takes your privacy very seriously.** This policy applies to all of the products and services offered by Subiz. Please read carefully this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information.

**1\. If you register for an account with us** , we may ask you for personal information such as name, surname, company business name, email, address, credit/payment card information etc… We will use your private information to provide the Services to you, send you notification of updates to the Services, send you marketing communications, not for any other purposes.

**2\. By using the Service** , you consent to the use of cookies, log information, clear gifs to: operate the Services, provide custom, personalized content and information; store your preferences and other information on your computer in order to save you time by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter the same information and to display your personalized content and appropriate advertising on your later visits to these sites.

**3\. We do not sell your personal data to the third parties.** We will not share your private information unless the obligation to disclose the information to third parties results from the currently effective provisions of law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

**4\. We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated** , non-personal information. Such information does not identify you individually.

**5\. If we are involved in a merger** , acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.  
Should you have any inquiries or doubts regarding our privacy policy or applied procedures feel free to contact us via the following e-mail: support@subiz.com
